[instrumental theme music playing]
[Maureen] There are eclipsing binaries,
astrometric binaries,
spectroscopic binaries.
It's hard to tell which one we're in
without a map of the star system.
-[John] You're doing it again.
-[Maureen] Doing what?
Shh.
[John] Using astrophysics
as a smokescreen.
Just tell me the bad news.
[Maureen] Okay, fine.
If this is our planet and this is a sun,
a typical orbit looks like this.
Okay, so I'm guessing
our orbit isn't typical.
[Maureen] The way the ecosphere
has been behaving,
the longer days
and the increased temperatures,
I couldn't figure it out
until I got up there and I saw this.
A coffee mug?
A black hole.
Hiding just off the shoulder of our sun.
The gravitational pull
is altering the orbit,
pulling our planet closer and closer,
until, when it makes this turn,
nothing on the surface,
I mean nothing, will survive.
How long do we have?
Till the planet becomes uninhabitable?
Weeks, maybe months.
It's hard to know
without more information.
So, we have a decision to make.
Do we tell people?
[John] You're asking me?
[Maureen] Yeah, I'm asking you.
[John] Honestly, I don't know.
I mean, God, Maureen,
you should have seen their faces
out there tonight.
Looking to me to answer questions
about that machine that I don't have.
So, tomorrow I get to clean up that mess.
-This one--
-It's okay.
I'll figure it out.
Whatever you decide, I'll support you.
[man]
Twenty-seven people died crashing here.
Husbands, wives, friends.
Dead because of what that thing did.
What about last night?
It was protecting us.
-It was defending itself!
-Who knows what would've happened.
-Maybe it can help us--
-Please! Enough!
One at a time.
Let's not have this devolve into chaos.
Victor, if I could make a suggestion.
Maybe we should hear from someone
who has seen, firsthand,
what this thing is capable of.
Angela, would you like
to tell us anything?
My husband was the seventh musician
chosen for relocation.
He played cello.
He loved football and hated the rain.
[voice breaking]
He was the best part of my life,
and that thing murdered him
in front of me.
So to be forced to sit here,
listening to people wonder
how they can use it...
sickens me.
I think the best course of action would be
to treat this as we would at home.
If a man had committed
any of these crimes--
But it's not a man.
Isn't that the point?
Angela...
I'm truly sorry
about what happened to your husband.
There is nothing that we can do or say
that can replace that loss.
But I think that it's important
that we understand
that the robot has changed.
-Changed? John, what are you--
-Let him speak.
Okay. Think of it like a computer
that's been rebooted or reprogrammed.
Look, I don't know
what the hell this thing was before,
or why it's here now,
but what I do know is
that the only reason
my daughter is alive today
is because that machine saved her life.
And it kept my family safe...
when I couldn't.
We're in a place where I think
we'd all like to feel a little safer.
[sighs] Yeah, and, uh...
what if it changes again?
Who's going to keep us safe from it?
You saw it for yourself.
It listens to my son.
So you'd put our safety
in the hands of a child?
It worked last night.
Only difference is,
now you all know about it.
Okay, everyone. I think we should try
and reach a consensus here.
[man] Let's begin with the fact
that we can't control this thing,
-nor do we understand it.
-[man 2] We might need its help again.
[chatter continues indistinctly]
-[Angela panting]
-Angela, wait.
I just wanted to say, you're not alone.
[stammers]
I lost a very dear friend in the crash.
I buried her with my own hands.
Very sorry to hear that.
[sighs]
It's good to see that you're on your feet.
I knew you were a fighter
when we found you.
When you found me?
Don West didn't mention
that I was there with...
I was the one who insisted that... [sighs]
Never mind.
Some people need to feel like a hero.
I'm just happy to see you're on the mend.
Well, thank you.
For what it's worth,
after trauma like you've endured,
it could be helpful
to speak with a professional.
I'm a therapist.
I'd be happy to help you--
[stutters] No, I appreciate it,
but I'm focusing on my physical therapy
at the moment.
Maybe some other time.
No problem.
Enjoy your walk.
[indistinct chatter]
-Souvenir?
-Ah, research.
If I brought some of that back, too,
would that be worth something to somebody?
Uh... only if you could keep it
from becoming contaminated.
Could you teach me?
[Naoko chuckles and speaks Japanese]
[continues speaking Japanese]
[Hiroki sighs]
-[in English] Not enough time.
-Oh.
[speaking Japanese]
[in English] Thank you.
[Don sighs]
Thanks. Oh, here.
[grunts] What's this for?
Protection. In case you didn't notice,
it's getting dangerous around here.
Last time a pretty lady
offered me protection,
-it was because we were--
-[footsteps thudding]
Maybe you should go back inside.
But I thought we could help.
I mean, there are a lot of heavy things
and he can--
Inside. Just until your dad gets back.
Go on.
Okay.
[footsteps receding]
[sighs]
[Penny] Having fun?
Uh... [sighs]
If you're wondering if rotting meat
smells the same here as it does on Earth,
then the answer is yes.
Well, I'm going swimming at the waterfall.
-We haven't tested the water yet.
-So?
So it could kill you.
Besides, I told my dad I'd do this, so...
All right, whatever. I'm gonna go.
You can come if you want.
[stutters]
[vehicle approaching]
Wait up.
[Vijay panting]
John, tell Maureen I'd like to talk to her
when she has a minute.
About what?
We're out of fuel, can't reach
the Resolute, audibly or visibly.
Might be time to consider the reality
of long-term habitation of the planet.
Right. I'll let her know.
-[Maureen] How'd it go?
-What'd they say?
-The robot stays.
-Yes!
But there are conditions.
You keep it away from other people,
you report any changes in behavior,
and register its whereabouts at all times.
Yeah, no problem.
I want to show you something.
[sighs]
-He doesn't get it.
-Let him be happy for a minute.
-Victor's outside. Wants to talk.
-[sighs]
You gonna tell him?
About what?
The coffee mug.
I made a list.
Stuff the robot could do to help people.
And then when they see how awesome he is,
they'll accept him.
Actually, I had something else in mind.
-Why don't you help me today?
-With what?
I'll tell you later.
It's kind of a father-son thing.
[footsteps approaching]
Actually, I forgot,
it's more of a father-son-robot thing.
John, are you forgetting something?
Oh, yeah. Right. We're heading off.
Man, those Robinsons
can be a real pain in the ass, right?
Always sticking their noses in--
-Sorry, do I know you?
-Don West.
I wouldn't expect a guy like you
to know a guy like me,
but you look like someone
who can get things done.
Talk to Peter Beckert.
He handles my affairs.
What if I told you
I knew where a man could get rocket fuel?
You know, enough to get everyone here
off this planet, back into space?
I'd say you were mistaken. Whatever fuel
was left in the Jupiters is gone.
Oh, the eels. Yeah.
Yeah, heard about them.
Ugh. [chuckles]
From what I understand,
those slippery bastards
need moisture to survive.
My crew and I, we crashed in the desert.
Auxiliary fuel tanks, untouched,
just sitting there,
waiting for a smart community leader
to claim them.
Dare I say, that man will be a hero.
And what would that make you?
Significantly wealthier.
You can arrange that, right?
[both speaking indistinctly]
[Don] Great. See you in a bit.
-[grunts softly]
-What were you two talking about?
Ooh, the future.
What's your schedule like
the next 24 hours?
Come on.
[Angela panting]
[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
[Maureen grunts]
[sighs]
Mom, what are you doing?
I'm just bringing some supplies
in case we have to spend--
You don't think you're going, do you?
Of course I'm going.
You need to rest. You haven't
given yourself time to properly heal.
I'm healing fine. I'll heal later.
I don't think you fully comprehend
how badly we need that fuel.
I fully do.
Which is why we can't bring anyone
whose physical limitations
might get in the way.
It's a straightforward thing.
We find the Jupiter, we transfer the fuel,
we bring it home. We got this.
Let someone else save the day for once.
-[chuckles] It's not that, it's-- [sighs]
-What?
Okay. Go.
Just make sure
you bring that fuel back safely, okay?
Just be safe out there.
You don't know what you might find.
Okay.
[sighs deeply]
-Reading anything interesting?
-[sighs]
I wish. [chuckles softly] Just work stuff.
Mmm.
Have many people been talking to you?
In a professional capacity?
Yeah, some. It's an unusual time.
Yeah. [chuckles softly]
Would you like to talk to me?
In a professional capacity?
-I wouldn't want to impose.
-Not a problem.
[chuckles softly]
Have you ever spoken
to a therapist before?
No. [chuckles]
You and John--
Oh, no, that wouldn't have worked.
Never know until you try.
[chuckles] Yeah, well,
it's a bit late for that anyway.
What's on your mind?
It's about you, actually.
Me?
I was wondering how you deal with it.
Being the keeper of all those secrets.
With all the things people tell you.
[sighs]
Oh, it's just... part of the job.
Don't you ever feel a responsibility to...
I don't know, tell someone?
I can't. Doctor-patient privilege.
[chuckles softly]
But...
What if you found something out
that really would impact
someone else's life?
I mean, how do you keep that in?
Look, here's the thing.
You have to find a place inside...
a little box...
where you put things
you don't want anyone else to know.
And that box has to be airtight,
so nothing gets out.
Once something goes in there,
it stays in there.
Where it can't hurt you... or anyone else.
It's the only way to survive.
-Okay.
-Why do you ask?
Is there something that you'd like me
to help put in your box?
[device beeping]
Dr. Smith speaking.
[Angela] It's Angela. We spoke earlier.
Yes, how are you?
If the offer still stands, I...
Sorry, it's a patient.
-Oh, yes. Oh, of course, yeah.
-Okay.
We'll talk again.
Okay, excuse me.
[sighs]
Yes, Angela. Where are you?
I'm at the Watanabe Jupiter.
I'll be right over.
[John] Come on, Will.
That's okay, but, uh, thanks.
We have ones like that back on Earth.
Whoa.
Thanks.
[grunts]
[chuckles softly]
[John] Will!
Coming!
You teach him to do that?
[Will] No. I guess he must've seen
one of us doing it.
I guess he's, uh... I guess he's learning.
Hmm.
-Hey, Dad?
-Yeah?
I just realized.
-I forgot to say thank you.
-For what?
Sticking up for him.
I wasn't sticking up for anybody.
I was just stating the facts.
But still.
Can you imagine what it's gonna be like
when we get to Alpha Centauri?
I'll be the only kid with his own robot.
Let's not get ahead of ourselves.
Penny's always saying
how she wants to write a book.
-Maybe she can write it about us.
-Will.
Sorry. What are we doing exactly?
[John] You'll find out when we get there.
Repaired about a hundred of these,
never once got to drive one.
But you do know how to drive, right?
-[distant explosion]
-What the hell was that?
[explosions continue]
-Must be gas, trapped below the surface.
-What, like a space fart?
They're called cryogeysers.
On Mars, they spit CO2.
On Triton, it's nitrogen.
Heat from the sun--
All right, whatever.
Is it safe to keep going?
As long as we stay up here
and don't drive
into the field of exploding rocks.
[Victor over radio]
What's going on? You guys lost?
That's a negative, Captain.
We're just plotting our course.
We're not here for sightseeing.
Let's move.
-[eruption booms continue]
-[grunts]
-That's the best idea this guy has had.
-How so?
Let's move.
["Panama" playing over speakers]
Don, this isn't a road trip.
It is now.
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
Whoo-hoo!
Wow, this thing can move!
♪ Jump back ♪
♪ What's that sound? ♪
♪ Here she comes
Full blast and top down ♪
[laughs]
-[man] Whoa, whoa, whoa.
-You're not supposed to open that.
Why would they put a sunroof
if we couldn't open it?
It's not a sunroof.
It's an emergency escape hatch.
Given everything that's happened,
don't you think
we deserve a little escape?
You know you wanna.
Come on, Doc.
Get up there, reach up to the sky.
Huh? Give us a "whoo-hoo"
like it's a limo on prom night.
-Yeah, well, I never went to prom.
-Seriously?
Yeah. I was studying for MCATS.
Then you, my nerdy friend,
have a lot of catching up to do.
-Up you go. Come on.
-[woman] Do it!
-Come on, Judy.
-Come on.
-[Don] Come on, Doc.
-[woman] Come on.
[man] Let's go.
Yes, finally. Loosening up.
♪ Panama ♪
-♪ Panama, Panama ♪
-Whoo-hoo!
♪ Panama ♪
You've got to be kidding me.
[Peter] What is she doing?
[woman chuckles]
It looks like she's having fun. Can we--
No, Diane, we cannot.
Get her back inside. Now.
Come back. Come back in.
Copy that, sir.
We're having visibility issues.
-We got bug ass all over the windshield.
-[Victor over radio] Enough, West.
Better pray that fuel is still there.
Seeing that this is our last chance
off this planet,
think we better all pray.
♪ Panama ♪
We're not much of an advertisement
for space travel, are we?
[chuckles]
It should come with a warning.
"Your trip to Alpha Centauri may cause
anxiety and high blood pressure.
Side effects could include
loss of communication,
eels in your fuel tank."
"Alien robots."
I'm sorry. I should have said something.
Especially to you, and I...
Yeah, understood. Personal choice.
[sighs]
There is something, though,
that I need to share with you.
You have family here, and I...
[sighs] You deserve to know that--
That they may not be safe here
much longer.
How... What? How did you--
Lucky guess. But there are signs.
Erratic weather patterns,
wildlife migration.
Even the oldest trees have only one ring.
The life cycle on this planet
is quite remarkable.
Birth, death, repeat.
Why didn't you say something?
It would have been irresponsible.
Cause panic.
You saw how they were
with your boy's machine.
And we're scientists, Maureen.
Just because we know something,
we're not compelled to broadcast it.
Information does not exist in isolation.
There's consequences. Context.
How do we tell our children?
If they come back with the fuel,
we'll all get off this planet.
Everybody will be happy.
Go dress your wounds, get some rest.
They'll need you when they get back.
[Vijay] How far are we going exactly?
Come on. Have you ever heard
of the phrase "carpe diem"?
Yeah, "seize the day."
But can't we seize it
from the safety of the Jupiter?
Where is your sense of adventure?
We're on an alien planet.
How much more adventure do you need?
Just, like, a little bit.
And if you will follow me...
-It's a cool waterfall, Penny.
-Shut up.
Where did it go?
It dried up. It's been getting hotter,
maybe the glacier melted.
[scoffs] This planet sucks.
It's not a big deal.
-We could go somewhere else--
-No, I had it all planned.
All what planned?
This. Here. You. Me.
I was gonna fall in
and pretend to be in trouble,
and then you would jump in and save me.
And we would be wet and laughing
at how stupid it was,
and then you would lean in and...
-And what?
-Nothing.
Come on,
it was just getting to the good part.
That's not funny. Forget it, it's ruined.
Don't say that. Well...
-maybe tomorrow we can do something.
-[Penny] No, we can't.
-We have plenty of time.
-No, actually, we don't.
We're stranded here, Penny.
We have all the time we want.
The planet is dying, okay?
What?
[Penny] I shouldn't have said anything.
I'm sorry.
What are you... What do you mean?
[sighs]
My mom says that there's
a giant black hole somewhere up there,
and all I know is that no one
and nothing is gonna survive it.
Are you serious?
We have to tell people. My dad--
No. No, no, no.
I'm not even supposed to know.
You can't tell anybody.
Please, promise me
you're not gonna tell anybody.
-Promise me.
-Okay, I promise.
Then let's go.
This doesn't make sense.
It was here. It was right here.
[Peter] I knew this was a mistake.
Maybe it fell.
You brought us all the way here for
"Maybe it fell"?
Deal's off, West. Let's go.
Everybody load up.
Maybe we'll get back before dark.
What does he mean, "deal's off"?
What deal?
-Nothing. It doesn't matter.
-[Victor] Oh, what, he didn't tell you?
Your pal here demanded money
to show us where the fuel was.
He's a real hero.
Don?
In my defense, it was supposed to be
a confidential-type arrangement.
This is about our survival,
life and death,
and you were holding it hostage?
Okay, so, when a doctor gets paid
for saving someone's life, that's okay.
-But when a guy like me--
-That's different.
Different how? If the fuel was here,
everyone would've been saved 'cause of me.
You get on a shuttle to the new world.
What do I get?
A hearty handshake
and a ticket back to a dying planet
with no future.
So forgive me, princess,
if I ask for a little compensation.
[metallic thud]
Did you hear that?
Oh, my God! It's here.
Hey, it's here!
Come here, we've been standing on it!
[both grunting]
[Judy] Look for the top hatch.
[panting]
[rumbles]
-[Judy] Whoa, whoa!
-Okay, whoa, whoa.
Whoa. Slow, slow, slow. Back up slowly.
See, I knew it was here the whole time.
We don't know if the fuel's still inside.
Don't count your chickens.
Oh, I won't be counting them, sir.
I only have the one. Her name is Debbie.
So, who's got the shovel?
[grunting]
[sighs]
According to the meter, tank's full.
Just like West said.
Apology accepted.
Fill her up. Let's get out of here.
[panting] This is amazing.
Yep.
But we're not here for the view, Will.
Then why did we hike up all this way?
Grab me a rock from over there.
Big one, bring it over here.
-Why?
-Just do it.
Come on, I need to go grab a rock.
Not him.
Just you.
Stay here.
-[Will grunts]
-[John] No, no, no, a larger one.
Big as you can carry.
[sighs]
[grunting]
Come on, you can do it.
[continues grunting]
Done.
Not quite. We need 26 more just like that.
What? [panting] Am I being punished?
No, no, no. I'm just...
I'm just trying to help you understand
that you have a responsibility now.
This is about him. Isn't it?
In a way.
But I already know what I'm doing, Dad.
I can control him. You saw.
He listens to me. He does what I say.
Will, he is not a tool.
I know. He's more than that.
He's my friend.
He's there when I need him.
But he wasn't always your friend, was he?
[whispers] No.
As much as we'd all like
to change the past,
undo our mistakes, we can't.
We have to live with our history.
So, in honor of that,
we're gonna place 27 stones here today.
A cairn.
A monument to all those
who lost their lives
in the attack on the Resolute.
You know, today, I...
I spoke to a woman named Angela.
She lost her husband on the Resolute.
This first one's for him.
[Smith] In order to release the pain,
you have to acknowledge its source.
Okay.
How do I do that?
[Smith] Words are a gateway
to your emotions.
I want you to start by sharing
what you remember about that day.
Well, like everyone else,
when the alarm went off,
we had no idea what it was for.
I remember Josh making jokes
so I wouldn't worry.
Tell me about the moment
where you first encountered the machine.
Outside the hangar,
there was panic, running, shoving.
At first, we thought
it's just the way people are.
Trying to be the first ones
to reach their Jupiter.
But then, we realized
they weren't running toward something.
They were running away.
That... thing was in there.
Anyone who got in its path,
it just... eliminated.
[Smith] You're doing great, Angela.
Now it's time to access
your sense memories.
I want you to lie down...
close your eyes.
I want you to focus on the sounds...
the smells.
[Angela] There's a strange metallic buzz,
like something very close,
except it's everywhere.
And then I smell burning.
[sniffs, voice breaking] People burning.
What do you see?
[Angela] Red. Emergency lighting.
So, it was hard to make out where we were.
Josh held my hand.
We tried to skirt the perimeter
to our Jupiter.
It was... It was so close.
And then...
he stopped.
[sniffles] His body went rigid.
[sobs]
He was hot, searing, white heat.
I couldn't let go of his hand. [crying]
It had burned into mine.
[crying]
I'm sorry.
Can we please not do this anymore?
Of course.
I think we've gone far enough
for this session.
I thought talking about it
would make me feel better,
but I feel worse. [crying]
[stammers] These things, they take time.
What if we don't have time?
Angela, I... I understand your anger...
that this thing...
that did this to your husband
is being welcomed among us.
But what prevents people
from moving on from tragedy
is a feeling...
that there's something they could do
to change it.
But there isn't. There simply isn't.
All we can do is hope, pray...
it doesn't happen to anyone else.
What if there is something I could do?
Something more than just hoping
and praying.
I'm sorry, Angela,
but I'm gonna have to ask you
to refrain from saying anything further
on this subject.
Maybe I should go.
-What?
-[sighs] We can pick it up tomorrow.
You can't just make me relive all that
and then--
I'm sorry. We can pick this up tomorrow.
[stutters] You can't just abandon me!
Dr. Smith?
[Angela sobbing]
-[sighs] Last one.
-Yeah.
Let me give you a hand.
No.
-[grunts]
-I, uh...
I should do this one.
[Will grunting]
[panting]
[grunting and panting]
[continues grunting]
[John sighs]
[sighs] Let's hope
we never have to add another one.
All clear! [echoing]
So, we good?
-Are you referring to our arrangement?
-Yeah.
We're good
when we get the fuel safely back.
What does that mean?
It means you need to stop standing around
and start helping.
How much longer?
Once we start the transfer,
about three hours.
Yeah, well, uh, let's try and make it two.
Would you like me to change
the laws of physics, or just lie to you?
Okay, everyone, listen up.
In just three hours, we're gonna have
a tank full of liquid methane
ready for transport. I...
What is it?
-Me?
-Mmm.
Yeah. I was just wondering
what we're gonna do
when the Jupiter falls off the edge,
takes the fuel tank with it?
Clearly we're hoping
that's not gonna happen.
Oh, you can have all the hope you want,
but gravity may have other plans.
You see, Vic, the west side of the Jupiter
is hanging over the edge.
Now, the auxiliary fuel supply,
that's on the east side.
As we transfer the fuel out,
the east side gets lighter.
The weight shifts to the west side,
sending it over the edge.
And since our hose
is connected to the tanker...
Okay, so do you have a better idea?
Or do you want us to pay for that, too?
We use the Chariots as an anchor.
We dig down,
attach the towlines to the Jupiter.
With the torque in the engines,
we counteract the shift in the weight.
-[Don] Hmm.
-Will that work?
It might. Just gotta get the right guy
behind the wheel.
Or right girl.
No offense,
but who do you expect to handle this?
Somebody who saves lives
or somebody who gambles with them?
No offense? How is that not offensive?
Don't let us down, Robinson.
[Penny]
I'm sorry I kinda freaked out back there.
It's pretty embarrassing.
Oh, um...
I almost forgot.
Everyone knows about the robot,
so guess I don't need that anymore.
Thanks.
Don't worry about it. Back there.
Everybody does embarrassing things
when they think they're gonna die.
Yeah, well, not like me.
Do you wanna know
why I didn't want you to see this?
It's something I wrote...
when our Jupiter was crashing
and I didn't think we were gonna make it.
Read it.
Really.
It's a poem.
Yeah, uh, a testimony.
In case anyone found our bodies.
"If you find this message, do not weep.
I have lived a life, I was not a creep.
I did not like books, but loved my guitar.
Brought my music to space
and traveled afar."
-This is terrible.
-[both laugh]
You try and rhyme
when you're hurtling to your death.
-Okay. [clears throat]
-[chuckles]
"I am Vijay Dhar, aged 16 years.
I loved free climbing
and I faced my fears.
I once had vertigo, but then overcame it.
Won a state-wide certificate
and my mom made me frame it."
[chuckles] It's from the heart.
"I have never been in love,
no girl broke this heart.
Seems my life is over
before it could start.
If you find this message,
please do not weep.
I'm just a particle of space dust
you don't have to keep."
I was gonna do the whole
"miles to go before I sleep" thing, but--
Shut up.
Can you tell me which direction
the Robinsons' Jupiter is from here?
North. About half a mile.
Thanks.
-You're walking?
-Yeah.
Do you have something to protect yourself?
Yeah, I do.
[engines whirring]
[engines revving]
How's your foot? Getting tired yet?
Not tired enough to keep me
from kicking your ass when this is over.
[Don] Can't we just skip this?
Go back to the part
where we're friends again?
West, I don't know how much longer
these are going to hold.
Go inside and tell Aiko
we need to disconnect now,
while we still can.
Aye, aye, Captain.
We're not done yet.
Pretty sure we are.
West, let's go!
You okay in there?
Yeah. You?
I'm not sure how much more I got.
Engine's running high.
Just hold on, okay?
Don's pulling everyone out.
-[Don] You guys almost done? We gotta go.
-Tapping out now.
-You get it all?
-[Aiko] Every drop.
Cool. See you topside.
[Aiko] Yeah.
[grunting]
[electricity crackling]
-[rumbling]
-Ow!
-[groaning]
-[electricity crackling]
[engines whirring]
-[rumbles]
-[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
[Don grunting]
Son of a bitch.
Let's go. Come on.
Let's go. Go, go. [grunts]
[ship creaking]
We're losing the Jupiter.
Prepare to detach.
-We need to do it simultaneously.
-What?
Judy, you won't believe what I found.
-Don? Where are you?
-[Don over radio] On my way out.
[Judy] Don, we can't hold it any longer.
Hurry up!
Detach on three. One, two...
No! No!
...three! Detach!
Whoa!
No, no, no!
[breathing heavily]
-[Judy grunting]
-[Victor] Detach!
-Judy, what the hell are you doing?
-Robinson!
West is inside.
Don, I can't hold it!
-You need to detach now, Judy!
-No!
Then I'll do it for you.
Don, no--
[panting]
[crashing]
No.
[stutters] He detached it on his own.
[continues panting]
He sacrificed for all of us.
[grunts] Are you crazy?
I don't even like you guys.
West?
[both panting]
[Don grunts]
[all panting]
See, I knew she was too much
of a goody-goody to do it herself.
And frankly, I was tired
of getting yelled at and blamed.
I don't wanna have to be responsible
for the Chariot going over, so...
Just gonna...
[stammering] But you were... How did...
'Cause I'm a badass, princess.
[chuckling] You're a badass princess.
-What? [stammers]
-[all chuckle]
No, no, no. There's a comma.
-You know, "I'm a badass, comma, prince--"
-[Judy] Yeah.
Yeah, whatever you say.
Yeah, oh, you're welcome, by the way.
Thank you.
Oh, um... Hi, Mom.
Hey. Where have you been?
Just hanging out.
Penny...
He seems nice.
[chuckles softly]
[Judy over radio] Mom, do you read?
Can you hear me? Mom?
Yes, Judy, hi. Go ahead.
[Judy] We got it, Mom. We got the fuel.
All of it.
[sighs]
Mom? [chuckles] Mom? Are you okay?
Yes, yes. I'm... I'm...
I'm good. I'm wonderful, actually.
Okay. Victor thinks it's too late
to trek home,
so we're gonna spend the night.
I just wanted to let you know.
Okay. Just get back safe.
[chuckles] I will. I love you.
I love you, too, honey.
Judy... great job.
[Judy chuckles]
Thanks, Mom. Bye.
-Oh, hey. How's everything back here?
-[Maureen sighs]
What is it?
We're gonna be okay.
[John] Four, four, four.
Five, five, five. Five. Okay.
So, what you're trying to do is,
you're trying to make pairs.
So you have to ask the other players
if they have any of the cards you need.
Seriously? Do you ever play fair?
I am so sorry
that I have excellent peripheral vision.
Hey, Smith, should we deal you in?
[chuckles softly] No, thank you.
[John] You got an eight?
[Will] Do you have--
[Smith] Uh, Will.
Why don't you ask your mom to join?
She's busy.
Said she had to do some calculations.
[Smith] The fuel doesn't get here
till tomorrow afternoon.
And when does she ever have the time
to just sit and play with you guys?
[Will] Okay, I'll go ask her.
Hey, don't worry. He'll be back.
I've never seen him make that face before.
-It looks like he's smiling.
-[chuckles softly]
Hey, Angela. What can I do for you?
Why don't we go talk outside?
[Angela] I have no quarrel with you,
Mr. Robinson.
You're doing what you think is best
to protect your family.
I'm happy to discuss this with you,
after my daughter has left the room.
Dad, no.
[John] Angela...
put the weapon down.
That's exactly why I'm here.
To put the weapon down.
Robot, leave the Jupiter.
[Will] Mom.
We're all playing Go Fish.
You wanna come?
Oh, honey, I'd love to but I've got to...
You know what? I'd love to.
Great, I'll deal ya.
[gunshots]
[echoes] Will! Will, don't go in there!
Will!
[gunshot]
[gasps]
[gunshots]
No!
[shuddering]
[monitor beeping]
A very hard head
is one of your dad's finest qualities.
He'll be all right.
Judy will check in on him
when she gets back tomorrow.
He just needs some rest.
[sighs]
Come on.
[Don] I don't know who she is,
but she's not Dr. Smith.
I had even more proof in my hand.
Photographs, diplomas.
Pictures of the man with his family.
Wearing the St. Christopher necklace.
-So why would she--
-I don't know.
But one thing's for damn sure.
You don't go through this much trouble
unless you have something to hide.
Don't worry, Angela.
No one will blame you for what happened.
It's all gonna work out fine.
[groans]
Hey.
[sighs] What happened?
It's okay. Everything's okay.
Where's Will?
You're the best friend I ever had.
You know that, right?
[Will sniffles]
I have to be responsible for you.
[cries] Step forward.
[gasps]
[slow instrumental music playing]